export const vocabulary = [
    { question: 'alpha', answer: 'α' },
    { question: 'beta', answer: 'β' },
    { question: 'gamma', answer: 'γ' },
    { question: 'delta', answer: 'δ' },
    { question: 'epsilon', answer: 'ε' },

    { question: 'zeta', answer: 'ζ' },
    { question: 'eta', answer: 'η' },
    { question: 'theta', answer: 'θ' },
    { question: 'iota', answer: 'ι' },
    { question: 'kappa', answer: 'κ' },

    { question: 'lambda', answer: 'λ' },
    { question: 'mu', answer: 'μ' },
    { question: 'nu', answer: 'ν' },
    { question: 'xi', answer: 'ξ' },
    { question: 'omicron', answer: 'ο' },

    { question: 'pi', answer: 'π' },
    { question: 'rho', answer: 'ρ' },
    { question: 'sigma', answer: 'σ, ς' },
    { question: 'tau', answer: 'τ' },
    { question: 'upsilon', answer: 'υ' },

    { question: 'phi', answer: 'φ' },
    { question: 'chi', answer: 'χ' },
    { question: 'psi', answer: 'ψ' },
    { question: 'omega', answer: 'ω' },
];